## Lawrence Colton Anderson

(801) 941-5161

Email: Anderson0741@icloud.com

Github: Anderson0741

903 E Carnation Dr

Web Developer with a background in sales and client relations creating hundreds of accounts over a 5 year period and maintaining one of the company's highest retention rates. Looking to apply recent training in front end development including JavaScript and React. Eager to learn new programming languages.

### **SKILLS**

Front-End	Back-End	Other Skills
<ul> <li>JavaScript</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>NodeJS</li> </ul>	• Git
<ul> <li>React</li> </ul>	<ul><li>Express</li></ul>	• JSON
<ul><li>HTML/CSS</li></ul>	<ul> <li>Mongoose</li> </ul>	• Sales
	<ul> <li>MongoDB</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>Customer Service</li> </ul>

### **GIT WORK**

# dev/Websites/leve\_up\_auto

I built a website for Level Up Auto with React App. The site is fully CRUD, and has user authentication so they can add posts, edit posts, and delete posts. As far as the CSS I used flexbox, and I used flex grid to align the content that I wanted in certain places and sizes.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Polished Image, Layton Utah - Detailing Technician

**April 2011 - January 2012** 

- Thoroughly cleaned cars
- Picked up and delivered vehicles

**Vivint, Texas** - Sales Representative | Product Service Consultant

March 2012 - 2014 / 2015 - 2017

- Installed home and business security systems
- Consulted home and business owners on their systems
- Set up the new accounts

Fuse Satellite, Nashville Tennessee - Sales Representative

May 2014 - October 2014

- Set up alternative TV services to save customers money
- Explained what they would get with Directv/Dish
- Trained new sales representatives

# **EDUCATION**

V School, Salt Lake City Utah - Web Development | Full Stack Javascript Developer 2017 - 2018

Utah Valley University, Orem Utah - International Business I Personal Finance

January 2012 - 2016

Weber State University, Ogden Utah - Associate's Degree

August 2008 - December 2009

Part of the New Century Program

Sandy, UT 84094